One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I grabbed hold, digging in my claws
te ni totte tsume o tateta
but the future
sono mirai wa
blurred together, colors running
nijimu iro ni kasunde mieta
A red that can swallow even summer's hues
natsu no iro mo nuritsubusu you na aka ni
bokura no koe kakikesareteiku you de
now attempts to blot out our voices
Move those halting feet of yours
tachidomaru sono ashi o fumidasou ze
Don't let stand the lies for show
misekake no uso yarisugosu yori
I'll give up countless mornings for my vows
nandome no asa chikai to hikikaeru yo
For the dream that we shared
bokura ga miteita yume
We do not have time, Saturn!
Vegapunk must not...
...be given license to speak!
I shall make the summons.
Starfall
What in tarnation is that?!
That’s...
...what happened
when St. Saturn made landfall earlier!
Who-ho-hoa there!
That’s where Stella and the others are!
I’m worried about them!
Better get in touch with Nami-san’s group!
Holy Land
Mary Geoise
Stella, what is that?
The dream of all mankind,
Vega Coffee!
Just drop a tiny speck
of this stuff in some water...
...and you’ve got nice,
hot coffee in an instant!
How many minutes do we have?
We aren’t on a strict timer per se...
Let’s wait seven minutes or so,
and then we’ll begin.
Though to be fair,
even if there is anyone wanting to intercept,
they won’t be within range to do so.
There’re five monsters now?!
〝Sandworm〟
〝Bakotsu〟
〝Fengxi〟
〝Itsumade〟
〝Gyuki〟
Highest Authority
of the World Government
What?! The Pacifista...!
It’s been downed?!
I saw something!
There’s something
racing along the shore!
A giant horse?
It vanished!
The Pacifistas over here
are no longer functioning!
Same here!
They’re being cut down?
No, seems like they’re partially frozen!
Hello?!
Nami-san, Robin-chan, et cetera!
It’s kinda hard to explain
what’s going on down here...
But basically, time’s up!
Get out of there any way you can!
Huh? Why?!
Sanji-kun, what do you mean?!
Reporting in!
Due to frozen cerebral circuits,
the downed Pacifistas are...
...temporarily disabled!
Someone did that for us?!
Now we don’t have to
waste strength on a lose-lose battle!
We have an opening!
Kill Bonney now!
Bonney and the Straw Hats
are at the northeast shore!
Half of the Pacifistas
are already disabled!
Definitely not the enemy’s doing!
Run fast and run away!
A really freaky monster’s
flying up towards you!
Just get out of there, now!
Hup!
Uhh? It’s gone.
It dug into the ground?!
Is it an earthworm?!
Sanji! This is Usopp!
Brook and Lilith are here.
The ship, though...
Well, it was a close call,
but it’s fine.
There! We’ve arrived safe and sound,
just as I said we would.
Don’t take credit!
It stopped thanks to Usopp!
Well, we wish we could
just get outta here right now,
but Zoro and Jinbe aren’t back yet!
Damn that mosshead! He’s still fighting?!
What a pain in the ass!
Jinbe!
What’s going on over there?!
I understand the urgency.
Whether they’ve finished fighting or not,
I’m dragging Zoro back with me!
Thanks, Jinbe! Sounds good!
You sense that Haki, too?
Almost makes you want to stop and look.
Yeah, it’s all over the island...
I see him!
And he’s still fighting!
That moron mosshead,
putting all of us in danger!
He’s a liability!
Hand Gun:
Spots!
Three-Sword Style:
Huhuva...
...Spot Hunt!
You see that?
I saw! A familiar sight!
A man ill-suited for dark places!
Let’s go!
Sun Saw!
Close call!
Awhuuuh?!
Hey, if it ain’t the ol’ Giant guys!
It’s been too long, Straw Hat!
We just couldn’t wait!
We had to see you again!
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop beep-beep-beep-bup-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipii pipopii, pipopiipii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep
Piipapii papipo, piipapii
No No No No No norenai
No, no, no, no, no, not feelin' it
kobiritsuichatte mou odorenai
I'm all stiff, all outta dances
My head feels so good, 'f I get unlucky again
atama Feel so good, mata Unlucky demo
Cola de fukitobase yowaki o
just gonna blow away the shy with a cola
Hey all you boys & girls! Looking good!
soko no Boys & Girls! omae ii yatsu
Hey all you boys & girls!
soko no Boys & Girls!
Update failed. I've had enough!
appudeto wa shippai kori gori
Wasn't it OK 'til yesterday?
kinou made nara seikai?
La la la la la la, run, run, run...
ran ran ran ran ran ran Run Run Run
"Hiding yet?"
mou ii kai?
You ready yet, up for a dance
junbi wa douyo odoreru no?
bukkowareteru kono jidai
in this broken era?
"Come find us!"
mou ii yo!
Spread out from here, drop into the world
koko kara kakusan sekai e Drop
Let loose on the stage of freedom and liberation
jiyuu to kaihou no Stage e
Those rising heads're punks!!!!!! No way!!!
wakiagaru atama ga Punk!!!!!! No way!!!
Sick of waitin', goof off and dance
matenaiyo fuzaketa Dance
Dopamine spilling over
afuredasu dopamin
The lonely singing in unity
kodoku ga tsudoi utau koushin
Bip-bip-bip-bup-bup-bup-bup-bupping
pipipi papapapapatteru
Can't can't can't count me out yet
mada mada mada horobinai
There's some stranger waving me over
shiranai dareka ga temaneki da
Smilin' so wide that it can't be real
uso mitai ni waratteru